<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ZZYW</title>
    <description>ZZYW is a New York based design &amp; art studio, specializing in interaction design.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 19:20:19 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 19:20:19 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ambition of Interactivity</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;content-container label-add-border&quot; id=&quot;joepage&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-lg-8 col-lg-offset-2 text-center&quot;&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
                    &lt;h1&gt;Ambition of Interactivity&lt;/h1&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;My article &quot;Ambition of Interactivity&quot; was published in the 2017 March Issurance of Blink Magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;Founded by Su Ye, in January 2014, at Florida, US, BLINK is a non-profit online journal that focuses on visual arts and literature.
BLINK's content contributors are from all over the world. Many of them are students, emerging artists and independent designers that are currently working overseas, including countries like United States, United Kingdoms, Germany, Japan, Australia, Spain and France, etc. Also, BLINK has a growing readers' community in China, which attracts new contributors from the creative communities from Beijing, Hong Kong and Wuhan. “Being an independent thinker&quot; is what BLINK aims at.
BLINK encourages the young Chinese-speaking generations to observe, think, and question today's art and everyday life with their critical eyes and thoughtful minds.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
                
                
                &lt;div&gt;
                    &lt;h2&gt;Excerpt of Magazine&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/ambitionofinteractivity/2018_blink_25-1.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/ambitionofinteractivity/2018_blink_25-8.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/ambitionofinteractivity/2018_blink_25-9.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/ambitionofinteractivity/2018_blink_25-10.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/ambitionofinteractivity/2018_blink_25-11.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/ambitionofinteractivity/2018_blink_25-12.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/ambitionofinteractivity/2018_blink_25-13.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/ambitionofinteractivity/2018_blink_25-14.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
			   &lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/ambitionofinteractivity</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/ambitionofinteractivity</guid>
        
        <category>curitoral</category>
        
        
        <category>research</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lifecycle of Interfaces</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;content-container label-add-border&quot; id=&quot;joepage&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-lg-8 col-lg-offset-2 text-center&quot;&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
                    &lt;h1&gt;exonemo: The Life-Cycle of Interfaces&lt;/h1&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;exonemo: The Life-Cycle of Interfaces will open on February 12 to May 4, 2018 at the New Media Artspace gallery in Baruch's Library and Information Building, 151 E. 25th Street.There will be a casual discussion with the artist for Baruch students on Tuesday, February 27th, 2018 from 6 to 8 P.M. in the New Media Artspace and room 415 of the Library and Information Building.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;The New Media Artspace will host an artist lecture and closing reception on Wednesday, March 28th, 2018 at 6 to 8 P.M. in Engelman Recital Hall, BPAC. Admission is free to all Baruch students. Tickets are $16 for the general public and can be purchased here. Entrance to BPAC is on 25th Street between Lexington and 3rd Avenue.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;The Life-Cycle of Interfaces is curated by Zhenzhen Qi, Assistant Adjunct Professor, in the Department of Fine and Performing Arts in the Weissman School of Arts and Sciences at Baruch College. The exhibition is made possible by support from the Baruch Computing and Technology Center (BCTC) and the Newman Library.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
                
                
                &lt;div&gt;
                    &lt;h2&gt;Curatorial Statement&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;For The Life-Cycle of Interfaces exhibition hosted at the New Media Artspace at Baruch College, the artists will exhibit a suite of four works:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/lifecycleofinterfaces/internet_yami-ichi.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    Documentation about selected works: Since 2012, Exonemo has been organizing Internet Yami-Ichi (Internet black market), a “backstreet of the internet”. Artists and creators are invited to occupy a flea-market styled exhibition space, and sell items that are interesting and unique to the internet. Originated in Tokyo, Internet Yami-Ichi has since spread out to New York, Berlin, Linz, Bursells, Amsterdam etc, totalling seventeen countries and continuingly to grow. “Once upon a time, the Internet was supposed to be a place for liberty.” Today, our relationship with the internet has become so intimate that we are bringing it to work, dinner, and into bed. Yet, many aspects of the internet also became more restrictive and foreign to us. The Internet Yami-Ichi invites netizens to step off-line, “browse face-to-face”, and reminisce about the wondrous naivete embodied by the early internet era. The documentation also recorded other works created by the artists, which wonder freely between spaces that are seemingly disconnected from one another.

                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/lifecycleofinterfaces/DesktopBAM01.png&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    DesktopBAM (2010) is a performance piece entailing programmatically controlling a mouse cursor to DJ on a desktop environment. It’s a homage to turntablism, born from using turntables in unconventional ways. The title BAM pays tribute to Afrika Bambaataa, a musician hailing from south Bronx, New York, one of the originators of breakbeat DJing and hip hop culture. The dynamism of this performance is created by the mouse cursor, controlled by computer algorithm, to moves faster and more accurately than any human DJ can possibly comprehend. The computational movements trigger the audience’s physicality, while at the same time evoke the “physicality of computers” controlled by humans in return.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/lifecycleofinterfaces/sscat-high.png&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    DanmatsuMouse (2007) humors with the idea of an electronic interface as an object of spirituality. The video records the process of destroying a physical mouse, while simultaneously capturing the motion of the trembling cursor desperately crawling across the digital screen, beckoning for a last bitwise appearance. The expressive movement of the cursor invites us to reconsider our relationship with a tool, an electronic device, or a technological object. Do tools exist for the purpose of helping its owner? Or do they leave behind traces of their own being? Could a tool serve as an interface crossing the immediate to the grandeur - an alternative space that’s ever expanding but never approaching?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/lifecycleofinterfaces/Fireplace.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
                    Fireplace (2014) is a video piece presenting scenes of burning optical mice and keyboards as tinder fed into a fireplace. In the old days of “hearth and home”, the fireplace was the center of the living room and family gathering. With the evolution of technology, fireplace was replaced by TV. In some countries, there are TV channels one can tune in to conveniently display video broadcasts of fireplaces. Entering into the era of hand-held devices, where everyone carries “smart” personal technology with them, PCs are joining the same fate as the fireplace, and other technological objects that are no longer desired. So, how about feeding retired PCs to fireplaces? To burn away yet another legacy as we shift to a new world of decentralized personal displays?&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;div&gt;
                    &lt;h2&gt;Artist Bio&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;Exonemo is a new media art collective formed by artist Kensuke Sembo and Yae Akaiwa. Initially established in 1996, they have developed a wide range of experimental works crossing freely between physical and digital, immediacy and virtuality—software programming, hardware circuit bending, multimedia installations, sound and image processing, live performance, networked objects and more. Playing with randomness and error, their work evoke a sense of humorous intimacy from tools and machines we usually think of as simple means to achieve finite goals. In 2016, their work “The Road Movie” won the Golden Nica for Net Vision category at Prix Ars Electronica. In 2012, the duo founded an internet secret society named “IDPW”, organizing “Internet Yami-Ichi (Black Market)” in seventeen cities across Asia, Europe and North America. They have been members of NEW INC, a museum-led new media incubator since 2015. Based in New York, traveling frequently between Asia and Europe for exhibition and collaboration, their work is constantly inspired by a renewed perspective on boundaries— whether aesthetic, cultural, geographic, or medium-based.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
                
			&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/lifecycleofinterfaces</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/lifecycleofinterfaces</guid>
        
        <category>curitoral</category>
        
        
        <category>research</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Playground</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;content-container label-add-border&quot; id=&quot;joepage&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-lg-8 col-lg-offset-2 text-center&quot;&gt;
				&lt;div&gt;
                    &lt;h1&gt;Richard Jochum: New Playground&lt;/h1&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;The New Media Artspace is pleased to present Richard Jochum: The New Playground. Richard Jochum: The New Playground will open on September 6 to December 1, 2017 at the New Media Artspace gallery in Baruch's Library and Information Building, 151 E. 25th Street.There will be a casual discussion with the artist for Baruch students on Thursday, October 4th, 2017 from 1:30 to 3:30 P.M. in the New Media Artspace and room 415 of the Library and Information Building.&lt;/p&gt;

                    &lt;p&gt;The New Media Artspace will host an artist lecture and closing reception on Monday, November 6th, 2017 at 6 to 8 P.M. in Engelman Recital Hall, BPAC and is free and open to the public.&lt;/p&gt;
                    
                    &lt;p&gt;Richard Jochum: The New Playground is curated by Zhenzhen Qi, Assistant Adjunct Professor, in the Department of Fine and Performing Arts in the Weissman School of Arts and Sciences at Baruch College. The exhibition is made possible by support from the Baruch Computing and Technology Center (BCTC) and the Newman Library.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
                
                
                &lt;div&gt;
                    &lt;h2&gt;Curatorial Statement&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;This exhibition highlights selected works from the artist, and utilizes digital media as a playground. Humorous yet profound, Richard Jochum’s work creates a temporary space and time. It enables audiences to leave behind immediate reality, and to observe, play, shape, and be shaped by a new opening in return. At a time that seems to be increasingly fragmented, Jochum’s work invites us to come together and play. “I think art continually has to create new images for he time we live in. For the conditions and issues we deal with: existentially, politically, physically, and globally. Searching such images is what I am aiming for. My artistic work is often based on participation or embedded in local communities. I believe in an intriguing encounter between art producers and the public. Audiences can make us learn better and see things we would not have known yet. I understand both intelligence and creativity to be profoundly social.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;
                    
                    &lt;p&gt;For The New Playground exhibition hosted at the New Media Artspace at Baruch College, the artist will exhibit a suite of four works completed between 2001 and 2017:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
                    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/newplayground/Halt2001_RichardJochum.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Halt (2001)&lt;/strong&gt; shows an artist climb a tree, sit on a branch, and pick up a saw in order to saw himself off the branch he sits on. He falls and lands on the same bough. The video is accompanied by sounds: birds twittering, sawing noises, and branch cracking.
                    

&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/newplayground/Snow2008_RichardJochum1.png&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Snow II (2008)&lt;/strong&gt; shows how the artist is rolling a ball of snow until he gets exhausted. The ball is growing and continues to grow after help arrives. But there is a limit to it; soon the group of helpers is bigger than the ball, thus making progress impossible.
                    &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/newplayground/20AD_GroupBark1_RichardJochum.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Twenty Angry Dogs (2010)&lt;/strong&gt; is a video and sound installation in which 12 performers bark like angry dogs. The selection comprises a group of people that is diverse in terms of age, race, gender, or profession. 12 screens are arranged in a circle, each playing an individual video. Viewers are encouraged to walk into the center of the circle to watch the looped videos. The site-specific piece has been installed using different set-ups and equipment. An additional separate video shows the group of performers barking together in “Group-Bark”. The installation reflects the relationship between humans and animals, and the raw emotional power that we all carry in us.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/newplayground/Catch_RichardJochum.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Catch (2017)&lt;/strong&gt;alludes to the childhood game of two people tossing cell phones between each other. The videos recorded by each of the two phones during the playful game are shown next to each other as a projection. Referring to a pervasive selfie culture, the recordings capture the players and their environment in topsy-turvy slow motion.
                    &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;div&gt;
                    &lt;h2&gt;Artist Bio&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;Richard Jochum is a conceptual artist working in a broad variety of media with a strong focus onvideo, interactive installation, performance, and photography. He is a studio member at the Elizabeth Foundation for the Arts and an associate professor of art and art education at Teachers College, Columbia University. He has worked in various media since the late 1990s and has had more than 140 international exhibitions and screenings. Richard received his PhD from the University of Vienna (1997) and an MFA in sculpture and media art from the University of Applied Arts in Vienna (2001). Richard’s art practice is accompanied by publications and research in the field of cultural theory, new media, and contemporary art and he has been awarded several grants and prizes. One of his latest projects in New York has been an interactive crossword installation with 27 video monitors, a web-interface, and crowd-sourced questions at the Made in NY Media Center by IFP in June 2017.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
                
			&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/newplayground</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/newplayground</guid>
        
        <category>curitoral</category>
        
        
        <category>research</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Introspection Game</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;content-container label-add-border&quot; id=&quot;tigpage&quot;&gt;

	&lt;div id=&quot;imagePlaceholder&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

	&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; src=&quot;/js/tig.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;

		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot; id=&quot;cover-page&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1&quot;&gt;
		
			&lt;p&gt;We are making the video documentary!&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;h1&gt;THE INTROSPECTION GAME&lt;/h1&gt;

			&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/island.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/interactiondemo/heartviz.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/interactiondemo/chapter3ani.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/interactiondemo/pulsesensorLED.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/interactiondemo/breathingpattern.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/ocean.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/outsidelogo.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/pulsesensor.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/room-setting.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/interactiondemo/chapter2ani.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/younguserandzz.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/ocean_oculus.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/interactiondemo/oceanwaves.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/darkroomandscreen.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot; id=&quot;big-p&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-md-8&quot;&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;A poetic narrative generated by your own body, The Introspection Game sends you to a journey within, using Oculus Rift, a breath sensor, and a pulse sensor.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;Participants are invited into &lt;a class=&quot;emptyroom&quot;&gt;an empty room&lt;/a&gt; one at time, wearing &lt;a class=&quot;waistband&quot;&gt;a breath sensor waistband&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class=&quot;pulsesensor&quot;&gt;a pulse sensor&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a class=&quot;3dheadmount&quot;&gt;an Oculus 3D head-mount&lt;/a&gt;. Once the Virtual Reality experience starts, the participant is temporarily teleported into &lt;a class=&quot;virtualroom&quot;&gt;a virtual space resembling the actual room he/she sits in&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;


				&lt;p&gt;Depending on the &lt;a class=&quot;breathingpattern&quot; data=&quot;true&quot;&gt;breathing pattern&lt;/a&gt;, the participant gradually descends upon &lt;a class=&quot;island&quot;&gt;a land surrounded by infinite ocean&lt;/a&gt;. As breaths become &lt;a class=&quot;oceanwaves&quot; data=&quot;true&quot;&gt;ocean waves&lt;/a&gt;, heart beats become both &lt;a class=&quot;heartviz&quot; data=&quot;true&quot;&gt;audible and visible&lt;/a&gt;, the participants gradually start to direct their attention inwards, becoming aware of less obvious body senses.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;!-- &lt;p&gt;As New Media Artists growing up under the influence of east asian philosophy, Yang and Zhenzhen have been fascinated by body as a medium of self knowledge. By connecting breath and heart beat with a slightly shifted narrative, the Introspection Game is an investigation into a new way of self speculation, which attempts to mediates, augment, and evolve our experience with the world around us.&lt;/p&gt; --&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;


		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-md-offset-5 col-md-4&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;The Narrative&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/c1-falling.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Fall from the room where the person sits in&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/e/e0/Black_Down_Arrow.png&quot; class=&quot;arrow&quot; /&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/chapter_2_processed_ending.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Fall through black void&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/e/e0/Black_Down_Arrow.png&quot; class=&quot;arrow&quot; /&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/island.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Arrive at The Island&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/e/e0/Black_Down_Arrow.png&quot; class=&quot;arrow&quot; /&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/tig/chapter_1_processed_1.png&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Get back to the original room.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/tig</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/tig</guid>
        
        <category>programming</category>
        
        <category>installation</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>exhibit: growth</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;content-container&quot; id=&quot;exhibit-growth&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot; id=&quot;bg-container&quot;&gt;

		&lt;div class=&quot;row avoid-overlay-plist-label&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-11 col-sm-8 col-md-6 col-sm-offset-1 black-bg&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;Exhibit:Growth is an interactive, immersive art installation Inside a stunning geodesic dome, you'll choreograph a unique visual expression via large-scale, motion-activated digital technology.
				&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;hr /&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Exhibit: Growth has seven stories: Liberation, Fear, Isolation, Frustration, Regret, Confusion and Inspiration. It explores the potential of using new media interactive technologies to evoke the feelings in its audience.&lt;/p&gt;
				&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;h3 class=&quot;col-xs-7 col-xs-offset-4 col-sm-6 col-sm-offset-5 col-md-5 col-md-offset-4 black-bg&quot;&gt;Made with Fake Love &amp;amp; the Mill+ for Umpqua Bank.&lt;/h3&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;


	&lt;/div&gt;
	
	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;style&gt;.embed-container { position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden; max-width: 100%; } .embed-container iframe, .embed-container object, .embed-container embed { position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; }&lt;/style&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;embed-container&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/120842719&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div id=&quot;slides&quot; class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/UmpquaBank_ConceptDev_092614-page4.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/UmpquaBank_ConceptDev_092614-page6.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/UmpquaBank_ConceptDev_092614-page8.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/UmpquaBank_ConceptDev_092614-page10.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/UmpquaBank_ConceptDev_092614-page12.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/UmpquaBank_ConceptDev_092614-page14.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/UmpquaBank_ConceptDev_092614-page16.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/UmpquaBank_ConceptDev_092614-page17.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/UmpquaBank_ConceptDev_092614-page18.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/UmpquaBank_ConceptDev_092614-page20.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/Umpqua_Schematics_v3-page2.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/Umpqua_Schematics_v3-page3.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/Umpqua_Schematics_v3-page4.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/Umpqua_Schematics_v3-page5.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/Umpqua_Schematics_v3-page6.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/Umpqua_Schematics_v3-page7.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/Umpqua_Schematics_v3-page8.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/Umpqua_Schematics_v3-page9.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/exhibitgrowth/Umpqua_Schematics_v3-page10.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/exhibitgrowth</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/exhibitgrowth</guid>
        
        <category>exhibition</category>
        
        <category>graphic_design</category>
        
        <category>installation</category>
        
        
        <category>design</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>is shame necessary</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;content-container&quot; id=&quot;isshamenecessary&quot;&gt;


    &lt;!-- header --&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;container avoid-overlay-plist-label&quot;&gt;

		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-10 col-md-offset-1&quot;&gt;
				&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-12 col-sm-6&quot;&gt;
					&lt;h1&gt;A experimental web design work for for New York University Professor &lt;a href=&quot;http://jenniferjacquet.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jennifer Jacquet&lt;/a&gt;'s new book &lt;i&gt;&quot;Is shame Necessary?: New Uses for an Old Tool&quot;&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/h1&gt;
					&lt;hr /&gt;
					&lt;h2&gt;We employed serveral new web technologies to explore the possibilities of delivering the message in a more precise and more playful way. &lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-12 col-sm-6&quot;&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;About The Book&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;An urgent, illuminating exploration of the social nature of shame and of how it might be used to promote large-scale political change and social reform.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In cultures that champion the individual, guilt is advertised as the cornerstone of conscience. But while guilt holds individuals to personal standards, it is powerless in the face of corrupt institutions. In recent years, we as consumers have sought to assuage our guilt about flawed social and environmental practices and policies by, for example, buying organic foods or fair-trade products. Unless nearly everyone participates, however, the impact of individual consumer consciousness is ineffective.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;!-- header ends --&gt;

	&lt;!-- images slide --&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;

		&lt;div id=&quot;landing&quot; class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;h1 class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-sm-7 col-md-5&quot;&gt;In the landing page, we used &lt;a href=&quot;http://p5js.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;P5.JS&lt;/a&gt; to create an immersive mouse-based interactive animation to give the user a primary understanding of this book. &lt;a href=&quot;http://isshamenecessary.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Try it.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;div id=&quot;navigation&quot; class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;h1 class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-sm-7 col-md-5&quot;&gt;In the main navigation page, we used &lt;a href=&quot;http://threejs.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;THREE.JS&lt;/a&gt; to create a special 3D navigation for the whole site. Three.js is a new 3D javascript library based on the newly released web technology &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.wikiwand.com/en/WebGL&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;webgl( Web Graphics Library )&lt;/a&gt;. It enables web developers to create 3D space on browser just like what video games do. &lt;a href=&quot;http://isshamenecessary.herokuapp.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Try it.&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/h1&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;div id=&quot;map&quot; class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;h1 class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-sm-7 col-md-5&quot;&gt;In Map of Human Punishment section, we explored the potential of using the new features came with CSS3 / HTML5 to create a film-like, narriative experience. &lt;a href=&quot;http://isshamenecessary.com/map&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Try it (desktop platform required).&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;!-- images slide ends --&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/isshamenecessary</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/isshamenecessary</guid>
        
        <category>web_design</category>
        
        <category>front_end_dev</category>
        
        
        <category>design</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FLOW</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;content-container label-add-border&quot; id=&quot;flowpage&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;

		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;h1&gt;FLOW&lt;/h1&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-md-5&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h5&gt;PROJECT BRIEF&lt;/h5&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;Virtual Reality experience about anxiety and detachment. Participant wears a breath sensor strapped to their waist, and a 3D head-mount, and get temporarily transported into a virtual world, running through grey abstract streets between sharp buildings, gradually submerged under the sea. A human voice then reassures the participant to not be afraid, and use deep breathing to detach and escape beyond what their eyes can see. It's been described by participants as &quot;a very emotional, cathartic experience&quot;. Not about sound bites and who can shout loudest and who wins and who loses, FLOW is an alternative new-media experience that attempts to bring back one of the most essential human qualities – the ability, through self-reflection, to detach from the physicalities around us, and transcend consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;h5&gt;BACKGROUND&lt;/h5&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;On Jun 2nd, 2011, a Beijing based journalist Peter Foster filed an article in the Technology section of the Telegraph – A 17-year-old Chinese boy sold his kidney for an iPad2 and an iPhone. Growing up with messages that we’re incompetent to make our own decisions, and that we will never be happy enough, the fantasy of rugged individualism start to sound particularly attractive. Today, we are working longer hours, buying more things, consuming more food and resources, but we are increasingly feeling exhausted, unfulfilled, and scared. We are running out of time competing against ourselves and each other. As new media artists, we ask the question - Is there a way to use new media technology to direct our attention inward, to be our own spectators, and remediate our relationship with our less conscious self?&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-md-5 col-md-offset-0&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/FLOW/setting.jpg&quot; class=&quot;img-responsive&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-md-5&quot;&gt;
				&lt;style&gt;.embed-container { position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden; max-width: 100%; } .embed-container iframe, .embed-container object, .embed-container embed { position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; }&lt;/style&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;embed-container&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/97007458&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-md-5 col-md-offset-0&quot; id=&quot;research&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h5&gt;RESEARCH&lt;/h5&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;We have always been interested in how new-media technology can help people gather more information to answer the questions – What am I like? What are my irrational thoughts and emotions that I wasn’t aware of? I was influenced by Harvard psychology professor Dan Gilbert’s research on synthetic happiness. In a recent study about human mind wandering (M.A.Killingsworth &amp;amp; D.T.Gilbert, 2000), Dr. Gilbert points out that people’s mind wander frequently, and people are in general less happy when their mind wander, regardless of what activities they are engaging in. The concept of mindlessness inspired my further research into ancient eastern philosophy, particularly techniques for practicing detachment, such as meditation, mantra, breathing techniques etc. I have also conducted research on biofeedback therapy and virtual reality immersion therapy (VRIT). A study conducted by Rauch, Eftekhari and Ruzek (McLay, et al., 2012) examined the effectiveness of Virtual Reality Therapy in treating military combat personnel recently returning from the current conflicts in Iraq and Afghanistan. With a sample of 42 combat servicemen who were already diagnosed with chronic PTSD (Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder), 20 of the servicemen observed a significant decrease of symptoms of PTSD after receiving Virtual Reality Exposure Therapy. Additional information about binaural and biofeedback testing can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://zhenzhenqi.wordpress.com/2014/02/15/flow/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;HERE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;


	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/flow</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/flow</guid>
        
        <category>programming</category>
        
        <category>installation</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Book of Happiness</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;content-container label-add-border&quot; id=&quot;book-of-happiness&quot;&gt;

	&lt;div class=&quot;container&quot;&gt;

		&lt;div class=&quot;row avoid-overlay-plist-label&quot;&gt;

			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-12 col-sm-4&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h1&gt;A book, inside which a person’s happy memories are represented and analyzed using Statistical Regression Analysis and Parametric Design.&lt;/h1&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;We interviewed a close friend of ours who has overcome more than a decade of struggle against depression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She lies down on a couch, and recalls 30 most difficult days during her journey. For each day she remembers, she rates her &quot;sense of loss&quot; and &quot;level of internal struggle&quot; on a scale of 1 to 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We processed the data through a parametric design algorithm, generated 30 diagrams, laser cut into 30 individual pages, and manually bind them into a physical book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this project, we want to explore the possibility of creating a new form of visualization that's both informative, and humane. We hope it could serve as a faithful account of a beautiful journey that's cherished by both the owner and the audience of this book.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;hr /&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-12 col-sm-8&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/1book.jpg&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;


	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;row gallery&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/1book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/2book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/3book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/4book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/5book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/6book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/7book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/8book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/9book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/11book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/12book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/13book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/14book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/15book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/16book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/book/17book.jpg&quot; /&gt;

				&lt;style&gt;.embed-container { position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden; max-width: 100%; } .embed-container iframe, .embed-container object, .embed-container embed { position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; }&lt;/style&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;embed-container&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/131484846&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

				
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/bookofhappiness</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/bookofhappiness</guid>
        
        <category>digital_fabrication</category>
        
        <category>graphic_design</category>
        
        <category>book_design</category>
        
        <category>installation</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Joe The Annoying Friend</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;content-container label-add-border&quot; id=&quot;joepage&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-sm-6 col-sm-offset-3 col-md-4 col-md-offset-4&quot;&gt;
		&lt;h1&gt;Joe The Annoying Friend&lt;/h1&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;Joe The Annoying Friend is a Chrome extension with an ON and OFF icon, so you can choose whether to let him talk. When you click on your own Status Updates or other people’s posts, he bluntly spits out insensitive facts like “Nobody is really special” and “Everyone eventually dies” to remind you to constantly check in with what’s real before getting sucked into the dreamland of “I wish life could be like this.”&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Download Extension&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/joe/onandoff.png&quot; /&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;Part of the Inspiration comes from my struggle with social psychology. Conversations help us bounce ideas and learn new things. However, we often end up feeding each other stories that make us bigger assholes without us realizing it. Neuroscientists have also discovered that learning process and outcome are stored separately in our brains. This could potentially make social interaction very dangerous – we arrive at conclusions and gradually lose associations with how we get there, or why we think it’s worth to get there in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;

		&lt;p&gt;In The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www3.nd.edu/~wcarbona/Haidt%202001.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Emotional Dog Wagging the Conscious Tail&lt;/a&gt;, Haidt mentioned about philosophers’ ability to self-reason, which may at times “reason their way to a judgment by sheer force of logic, overriding their initial intuition.” This concept got me really interested. So, it’s like having a friend who you can always reason with, without worrying about the social conformity issue. Thus, the birth of Joe my annoying friend.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/joe</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/joe</guid>
        
        <category>programming</category>
        
        <category>web</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>balance</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;content-container label-add-border&quot; id=&quot;balance&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;container-fluid&quot;&gt;
		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot; id=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-10 col-xs-offset-1 col-sm-8 col-sm-offset-2 col-md-6 col-md-offset-3&quot;&gt;
				&lt;h1 class=&quot;avoid-overlay-plist-label&quot;&gt;BALANCE&lt;/h1&gt;
				&lt;p&gt;BALANCE is an interactve web project. We created two interactive animations by Javascript. Users could change the variable within a range and create their own version of a &quot;balanced shape&quot;. They can also submit the shape they created to our database and get their own shape 3D printed out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BALANCE is a collective internet art piece that involves big data, digital fabrication, parametric design and psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://thebalance.herokuapp.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;VISIT BALANCE LIVE SITE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
				
				
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;


		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot;&gt;
			&lt;style&gt;.embed-container { position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden; max-width: 100%; } .embed-container iframe, .embed-container object, .embed-container embed { position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; }&lt;/style&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;embed-container&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/89470698&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;


		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot; id=&quot;intro-posters&quot;&gt;
			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-6&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/balance/poster-landscape.jpg&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-6&quot;&gt;
				&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/balance/poster-portrit.jpg&quot; /&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			
		&lt;/div&gt;


		&lt;div class=&quot;row&quot; id=&quot;learnmore&quot;&gt;

			&lt;div class=&quot;col-xs-12 col-sm-8 col-sm-offset-2&quot;&gt;
				&lt;!-- &lt;hr&gt; --&gt;
				&lt;h1&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://thebalance.herokuapp.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;try the interactive animations on live balance site.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
				


			&lt;/div&gt;
			
		&lt;/div&gt;





	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/balance</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/balance</guid>
        
        <category>front_end_dev</category>
        
        <category>interaction_design</category>
        
        <category>database</category>
        
        <category>graphic_design</category>
        
        
        <category>art</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
